[Music]
Let's play the game of news, it is the news that brings down the
movement of shares, it spoils the movement of shares, it is the
news that makes you
rich, we have brought some such news
where the shares are getting impacted, let's
see one by one, let's bring it on the screen, the
first company is ah, let's bring it quickly, one
after the other, let's go with great force, there will be a
consideration on issuing bonus shares, ah, HDFC Bank can do it.  The
company's board meeting is on July 19.  I
think the company's results will also be declared on the same day
and the decision will be taken on the same day.  This morning, very
good momentum was seen in HDFC Bank.  A
decision may also be taken on issuing interim dividend.  Ah sir, right now it was
trading almost flat and was trading above 2015 in the morning.
Set a high for 2022-23.
Sir, what will be your view on HDFC Bank?  No
doubt, see Vipul ji, I
am positive on HDFC Bank and I think that the
stock should be in your portfolio
and many stocks are discussed during the sessions
where there is no liquidity
but a bank like HDFC Bank
is the number one bank among private players, I think
and I was watching this news of bonus in the morning itself,
so this is going to be a very positive
sentiment, so I think
you should stay with it, you can buy from the current zone also and it is
currently trading with a good structure,
continuously higher high closing on monthly basis, on
weekly basis, the chart is positive, so
2152200,
I think it is going to come in the next three to four months
and if HDFC Bank goes then
only the bank will show the next direction to Nifty, so
definitely you should have it.
Okay, let's quickly bring the next company on the screen.  Let's
see what
news is coming out here.  Ah, so bring it
on the screen.  HDb Finance's
results have come out today and it has also been
in the news continuously since its listing.   The
results have not lived up to expectations.  The pressure
is visible.  Specifically, profits have
declined by around 2.5%.  Net
interest income has also seen an increase of 18%.
But NIM has remained
almost flat.  So sir, what
will be your comment?  Right now if you look at HDB Financial Pay, there are
a lot of queries regarding this.
What will be your comment on this Sir?
Vipul ji, I had told you this morning itself to
maintain a stop loss around 810 809.
Look exactly 809 put a low deep of 9.05.
So I think it's
running around 815.  Whatever investors were
holding for IPO listing, they did
not sell the goods on listing and
got allotment and even after that you have buying.
I think 810 810 should be
your stop loss on a closing basis.  You
will see that if
any stock does not sustain above the IPO high, then there are
two types of things associated with that stock.
One doesn't work.  Otherwise it comes down very low.
So I think there is
value somewhere in HD B Finance and
I think that value is going to go around 950.
But it should be supportive with the price action.
If it is not being supportive with the price action, then
you may feel some pain later.
So that is why my view here is that
maintain a stop loss at 810.
Rest stay tuned as it is around 810 only.  If you
want, you can also book profit once from Current Zone and
leave.  A
fresh rally is about to come above 850.
So right now the stock will not last for two, three or four weeks.
Yes, so this matter is
coming out regarding HDFC HDB Financial.
Which is the next company where there is news
because that is HDFC L, well look at this,
keep an eye on it and in this entire sector, all these
insurance companies are
seen working in good momentum today and good days are coming for them, the
net profit has increased by 14%, here
if we look at the income from net premium,
there has also been an increase of 16%, it has increased from 12510 to
1446 and apart from this, if
you see here then the results are better than expected, please
show the prices on the screen
once.  So the momentum
seems to be building well here.  Sir,
what will be your comment?
What should I do now regarding HDFC Life?  Currently it is
trading almost flat but
other companies in this sector which are
related to the insurance sector have good momentum.
Sir, today I am positive for the medium term and long term.
But you will see that the
chart of HDFC L has been very volatile
in the past and the results are coming out good sir.
This theme sir, there was not that much rally.  You
will see that in comparison to this, SBI Life
seems a little better to me.  Rest see,
I would like to go with HDFC also.  In the morning I thought the
target was 950. The broker said Harsh ji was
talking to me and I also agreed.  So
I think that Sir, the fundamental value
is there in it but it is so volatile,
hence you should buy it with a fair valuation.
Currently running around 758.
You can invest 40-50% at a time from the current zone.
If you want to
invest in this stock.  Otherwise once it
comes around 735 730 then buy on deep and
go.  In this case my stop loss will be
685 and once the target is reached, I
think for both the targets 850 and 950
you have to keep a minimum plan of 6 to 8 months.  It remains
very volatile and
deceives even after the breakout.  Such
nature has existed in the past also.  So you have to be very
clear about that that this nature
is going to continue in the future also.
We want you guys to keep this in mind.  Please bring one such long one
quickly.  ICICI Mud Pay
results have also come today.  Let's see what situation you see after the results.   The
pressure is visible.  As a result,
profits have increased significantly.   There has been an
increase of around 29%
in net profit.  Their net premium has increased by 14%.
So Sir, right now the pressure
seems to be increasing in Lobert,
Sir, the entire segment did not move that much
and I think there is still some
consolidation left in it, so see, it
is down only for 25 points, I think
I am expecting a little more downside here,
1940 1935 is coming soon,
so those who have it, stay tuned,
that is it, Sir, the entire theme, you will see that it is
a little volatile, so this thematic which is a
sentiment, it has become ICICI, SBI L
, HDFC L.  So all these stocks are
very volatile and
move with a season and even now see, the one which was
coming up from the down side with momentum, almost
around 1650 1700, is making a base from there and is
coming up slowly.  Right now I
feel that consolidation is going to continue here for another one or two weeks.  A
little bit below
you should buy on deep.  But
immediately in two, four or five months, the ah will come up
and you will get a lot of profit.  This will
not happen.  is not gonna happen.  So make sure that
if you are investing in a life insurance or general insurance company, you should have a
minimum view of 1.5 to 2 years.
That too should be bought with fair valuation.
I think there are possibilities of them coming down a little further.
Correct.  This advice is being given to you here.
Now let me bring you one more share where there is
news but there are many
questions from the viewers also.  Let us tell you that
big news has come out.  Jio BlackRock has been
given approval to launch four new money funds.  SEBI has approved the launch of four new money funds
and this is a big
news coming out here.  Now
gradually a lot of momentum is being
seen building up here.  All four funds will be
in the direct plan.  Also, let us
tell you that this will give investors an
opportunity to invest in equity at low cost and among the four funds,
Jio BlackRock Nifty Mid 150 Index
Fund is one.  Jio BlackRock NFT Nex50 Index
Fund.  Ah Jio Black Rockk is SALAC 250
Index Fund and Jio BK Rockk NFT is 8 to
13 G Securities Index Fund.  These are all the
funds in which you can invest.  A
decline of around half a% is being seen.
Sir, a lot of news updates are coming.  Can I
enter Jio Finance even at Rs 302
?  And what should those who have Jio Finance do
?
Look, those who have it, you stay and remain worry free.  There
is no need for you to sell it.  But I think already na has become a
top.  A shooting star has
formed on a weekly basis almost around 38 340
and I think it is around 39 day low right now.
Wait once.  Fresh
entry will start from Rs 305.  From 305 to
290 that one I think Fair
Valuations might be for you.  The rest of the
news is positive.  The fundamentals are strong.  It has come so high
in such a short time, that is
why I will wait once.  So the
rest who have it, stay tuned.  My
target is one and a half year sir, minimum I think
550-600 is also possible.  The way
the news is, the way the theme is.  But
now there is multiple time resistance, that
resistance will also have to be crossed.
After that the stock is going to go up.  Hence,
for a fair valuation, I would give
this counter a once-over.
Okay, sir.  And those who have it can hold it,
right?
Definitely.
We're going okay.  And let us tell you that this is about the
share of Jio Finance which is
trading around Rs 320.  But now what should be done with Jio
Finance's mutual fund and these
four new funds that are being launched
?  You should invest money or not.
What should be the strategy?
We are coming with two special guests at
4:00 pm.  And see,
Viral Bhatt, Narendra Solanki ji
will be our special guest and he will tell you that
Jitendra Solanki ji of Jio will be present with us.
What to do and what not to do in Jio's new equity fund.
Understand this entire strategy at 4:00 pm.  Harsh and Divya will be present with you.  To
support you in this strategy and to
convey your questions to the audience experts.  So
you have come to our special
program Jio with Viral Bhatt and Jitendra Solanki.  Don't forget to look at equity funds.
Our segment is important.  Let's quickly bring up the next company
and see if there's any more
news coming out.  Pretty
fantastic news.  One can also quickly cover Just Dial.
Sir, results of jstale have also
come.  Profit has increased by 13%.
6% increase in revenue.  EBITDA increased by 7%.  Is there
any scope, sir?
What should I do now in Just Dial, sir?  There is a decline of 4% now.  The
results did not meet expectations.
Look Sir Ja Dial I have been watching it since then.
I think from 2014-2015, at that time it was trading, I
think almost above 1000.  Ok.  At
that time the trade used to take place around 1350-1400.
Many times we have seen consolidation happening
and there is a past record of moving 15%-20% in a single day
and now
look at it, today it is down by 4%, so I do not have
confidence in this stock no matter
how good the result is because it has
cheated so many times and that is why I will
avoid it for once, those who have it, I will
say that you should exit once
because this stock does a lot of consolidation.  There
is still potential to come down.  I think there is potential for 850-860 also.
Otherwise,
I will not advise you to buy it at this counter.  I will
not say bye now.  Whenever it comes around 815 820 then
I will buy at that time and
that too with a stop loss of 760.
But I will not say bye at all in this zone.   So let's start with
this thing coming out about Just Dal.
Another company that many
people have questions about.  One thing
we discussed in great detail this morning is
Wari Energy.  Let me tell you that whatever is there
in the renewal, please forgive me.  Before the results are out, a
very good momentum is being seen here.
Today, a rally of about 10% has been seen in intraday
within the renewal of the price and a great move has been seen here
within just two trading sessions, where
instead of giving a return of about 4%/8%, a return of 26% has been seen
and it has reclaimed the level of 1000 again.
In fact, now it is
not 1200, I think you have
not calculated the lower price correctly.  This Vari Renewal
technology is installed below.  Come on sir,
what should I do now for the renewal of the bill?
Look, I think you should stick
with a stop loss.  Stop loss will be 1150
and I think look, today it is
in momentum, it was there yesterday also.  Deep can be found once.
But don't sell that deep.  There is time for further accumulation in that deep.
And today the
high was also around 1267.  You did it the morning after too.  At
that time I had said that it was 10%
up.  If Vipul ji ever comes down,
I will say bye.  He just
came around the buying zone once I think.
If you buy the stock then I think
1450 1500 is coming soon and you should buy it at a deep price.
You will get to see 1180 1170 once, if not today then tomorrow.  So
wait for that once.  Right now, this level
which was so high is coming down a little bit.
So we need to respect the price
action.  Wait once before leaving.  Not now.
Wait once before leaving.  Okay, last counter
sir, today is about the news and there are
some updates regarding Yes Bank,
quickly look at the screen, here
SMPG can make an additional investment of Rs 9100 crore,
some such reports have come in this morning,
Sui Financial Group is considering additional investment in
Yes Bank,
so now again after a long time,
ah, the update is coming, Japan's second
largest bank had invested in the bank 2 months ago
and now there is
talk of additional investment there.  Carlyle Group may
try to buy the remaining 5% stake from small shareholders.  Now, there is a
slight doubt among some people that
how confirmed is this news or not because it is
quoting Bloomberg, so once it is
confirmed, I think one should take it with some
caution.  Sir, what would be your comment on Yes Bank
and along with this, we have a
viewer Nidhi Marda ji, she has
sent us money and is saying that you are asking
questions for a long time, hence the time has also passed.
Gabriel's call asking
what to do with the one you gave me two days ago
?  So cover both Yes Bank and Gabriel
together.
See, I have given statement for Yes Bank earlier also.
Lastly, I will
say that there is a song in Punjabi called
Turuk Turuk Tuk Tara, after that there is Na Na
Re.  So, I have no response for Yes Bank,
sir.  So it has happened many times that Yes Bank has cheated me,
so I would not like to go with Yes Bank at all.
Those who have it, stay put
with a stop loss of 17.50
and Gabriel's call right.
So ok, right now it is running around 1037 and
I think I will have to check once
in this Excel sheet of mine what target and stop
loss I had given for it, if I do
n't see it then I will not be able to tell what it was
exactly right now.  Exactly,
give me a second.  Ah, its first
entry price was 1070, target was 1085,
second target was 1130 and third target was
1135, okay, so see, it is running around 1037 now,
I think if you do not do anything then
wait once,
maintain a stop loss around 1005, stay put, the
structure is good, there is no such problematic
situation,
yes there is some disclosure, sir,
see, whatever stocks I have discussed,
I do not have any personal holding in any of them, a
lot of stocks have been
discussed.  Our model portfolio
products are already recommended to our clients.
Investment and Securities
Market is subject to market.
If you are investing in any stocks, you should
kindly do it after consulting your personal advisor and
studying yourself.  Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.  Thank you for
joining this discussion today.
[music]